<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Theme Features on Alison Hill</title>
    <link>https://alison.rbind.io/categories/theme-features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Theme Features on Alison Hill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alison.rbind.io/categories/theme-features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The netlify.toml File</title>
      <link>https://alison.rbind.io/blog/2019-02-spoonful-netlify-toml/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alison.rbind.io/blog/2019-02-spoonful-netlify-toml/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Just a spoonful of Hugo helps the blog go down.&amp;rdquo;
  me, only somewhat kidding  You can read the previous post about my &amp;ldquo;Spoonful of Hugo&amp;rdquo; series here. In this series, I&amp;rsquo;m sharing small spoonfuls of Hugo that I have learned that hopefully can help you get your site UP (and even better- more efficient, more streamlined, more automated).
This is my second post in this series, and it is a relatively quick one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Page Bundles</title>
      <link>https://alison.rbind.io/blog/2019-02-spoonful-bundles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alison.rbind.io/blog/2019-02-spoonful-bundles/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Just a spoonful of Hugo helps the blog go down.&amp;rdquo;
  me, only somewhat kidding  In this series, I&amp;rsquo;m sharing small spoonfuls of Hugo that I have learned that hopefully can help you get your site UP (and even better- more efficient, more streamlined, more automated). You can read the previous posts about my &amp;ldquo;Spoonful of Hugo&amp;rdquo; series about Hugo archetypes and Hugo versions.
This is my third post in this series and it is breaking news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Spoonful of Hugo</title>
      <link>https://alison.rbind.io/blog/spoonful-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alison.rbind.io/blog/spoonful-hugo/</guid>
      <description>** No content below YAML for the series _index. This file is a leaf bundle, and provides settings for the listing page layout and sidebar content.**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Archetypes</title>
      <link>https://alison.rbind.io/blog/2019-02-spoonful-archetypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alison.rbind.io/blog/2019-02-spoonful-archetypes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Just a spoonful of Hugo helps the blog go down.&amp;rdquo;
 me, only somewhat kidding   As a happy blogdown user, a common story I hear from other #rstats users is that you try to change one little thing in Hugo, and the whole site breaks. Here be dragons for folks who aren&amp;rsquo;t web developers.
I&amp;rsquo;m here to tell you that there are small spoonfuls of Hugo that can help you get your site UP (and even better- more efficient, more streamlined, more automated), even if you are not in the least bit interested in transitioning into a career in web development 😏.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
